



 

   //Questions array

   let questions = [

    {

         number:1,

         question: " ___ is a short piece of writing that discusses, describe the analyses one topic",

         answer : "Essay",

         options : [

                          "Essay",

                          "Prose",

                          "Speech writing",

                          "Novel"

                        ]

    

    },

    {

         number:2,

         question: "Every good essay must be marked by these except",

         answer : "Variety",

         options : [

                          "Clarity",

                          "Unity",

                          "Variety",

                          "Coherence"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:3,

         question: "A good essayist should have adequate knowledge of",

         answer : "Paragraph development",

         options : [

                          "Topic sentence",

                          "Sentence construction",

                          "Punctuation marks",

                          "Paragraph development"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:4,

         question: "___ gives the reader idea of what the essay is all about",

         answer : "Introduction",

         options : [

                          "Prologue",

                          "Introduction",

                          "Subject matter",

                          "Thesis statement"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:5,

         question: "An introduction of an essay leads the reader to",

         answer : "Thesis statement",

         options : [

                          "Main body",

                          "Subject matter",

                          "Thesis statement",

                          "Narrative"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:6,

         question: "___ purports the writer’s point of view",

         answer : "Thesis statement",

         options : [

                          "Main body",

                          "Subject matter",

                          "Thesis statement",

                          "Narrative"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:7,

         question: "The logical order of ideas include these except",

         answer : "Coherent order",

         options : [

                          "Chronological order",

                          "Spatial order",

                          "Emphatic order",

                          "Coherent order"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:8,

         question: "In which logical ordering of ideas is the least important idea presented before the most important one",

         answer : "Emphatic order",

         options : [

                          "Chronological order",

                          "Spatial order",

                          "Emphatic order",

                          "Coherent order"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:9,

         question: "In a narrative essay the writer present his ideas in __ order",

         answer : "Chronological order",

         options : [

                          "Chronological order",

                          "Spatial order",

                          "Emphatic order",

                          "Coherent order"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:10,

         question: "The narrative essay is ___ in style",

         answer : "Conversational",

         options : [

                          "Conversational",

                          "Expressive",

                          "Story telling",

                          "Figurative"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:11,

         question: "The descriptive essay presents a __ of a subject in the mind of the reader",

         answer : "Pen picture",

         options : [

                          "Distinct image",

                          "Clear idea",

                          "Impression",

                          "Pen picture"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:12,

         question: "___ type of essay is not influenced by writer’s feelings, prejudices, attitudes or impressions.",

         answer : "Objective description",

         options : [

                          "Objective description",

                          "Subjective description",

                          "Perceptual description",

                          "Logical description"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:13,

         question: "___ type of essay lacks authenticity of facts and figures",

         answer : "Subjective description",

         options : [

                          "Objective description",

                          "Subjective description",

                          "Perceptual description",

                          "Logical description"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:14,

         question: "Which of these is an example of a descriptive essay topic",

         answer : "A football match",

         options : [

                          "An accident I witnessed",

                          "A memorable day in my life",

                          "The election day in my town",

                          "A football match"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:15,

         question: "Which of these is an example of a narrative essay topic",

         answer : "My experience in the jungle",

         options : [

                          "My experience in the jungle",

                          "A place I would like to visit again",

                          "My English lecturer",

                          "The person I admire very much"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:16,

         question: "In argumentative essay__ is the watchword",

         answer : "Logicality",

         options : [

                          "Persuasion",

                          "Logicality",

                          "Coercion",

                          "Validity"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:17,

         question: "In what kind of argument does the writer appeal to the reasoning of the audience through logic",

         answer : "Pure argument",

         options : [

                          "Deduction",

                          "Pure argument",

                          "Persuasive writing",

                          "Inductive reasoning"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:18,

         question: "In what kind of argument does the writer excite the emotions of his audience",

         answer : "Persuasive writing",

         options : [

                          "Deduction",

                          "Pure argument",

                          "Persuasive writing",

                          "Inductive reasoning"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:19,

         question: "The primary function of an expository essay is not to convince or persuade the reader but to __",

         answer : "Explain something",

         options : [

                          "Describe something",

                          "Narrate something",

                          "Expose something",

                          "Explain something"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:20,

         question: "Which of these is not a step involved in pre writing stage of an essay",

         answer : "Essay restructuring",

         options : [

                          "Choosing a topic",

                          "Generating ideas",

                          "Essay restructuring",

                          "Developing the thesis statement"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:21,

         question: "Criteria to be considered for topic selection in essay writing include these except",

         answer : "Type of essay",

         options : [

                          "Careful Reading",

                          "Knowledge of the topic",

                          "Interest",

                          "Type of essay"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:22,

         question: "The hallmark of a well-organised essay is a ___",

         answer : "Thesis support structure",

         options : [

                          "Thesis support structure",

                          "Adequate paragraphing",

                          "A good topic",

                          "Logical coherence"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:23,

         question: "The best time to think about how to organise your paper is during the__",

         answer : "The prewriting stage",

         options : [

                          "The prewriting stage",

                          "The publishing stage",

                          "The organising stage",

                          "The writing stage"  

                          ]

    

    },

    {

         number:24,

         question: "The last stage of essay writing is",

         answer : "The publishing stage",

         options : [

                          "The prewriting stage",

                          "The publishing stage",

                          "The editing stage",

                          "The writing stage"  

                          ]

    

    }

     ];   